Mine.
Are we looking a bit pathetic?
I'm not looking like this.
I'm not looking, Mom.
Amitabha.
I dare not open my eyes
Hope it's just my imagination
Use the Light-Up Card.
It's fine.
Not scared at all.
Let me do it.
Who spoils you? Everyone spoils me.
Everyone has to spoil me
Ding Pudding
I love you so much!
Act cute.
Act cute, then.
Beg me.
Beg your bro.
What the heck?
Call me bro.
Bro can't take it anymore
So, are you treating me or not?
What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is still mine.
And a new big bro.
Right.
Second bro.
Second bro, you're the killer.
I was raised on bragging.
Then I'll Shoot down you.
Baby Ding
Didn't you buy something with your car keys?
Baby Ding is being framed!
Sis.
Are you mad?
You.
Don't ask so many whys.
Why are there so many whys?
Why?
Whose dad am I?
Or am I the dad of all four of you?
Call me, call me.
Hurry up and call me.
Ding Ning is awesome.
Truly awesome.
Hey.
Give it to little bro.
Let little bro do it.
Let's go.
Absolute king.
Awesome.
Little bro is amazing.
The undisputed king of games.
Can this photo be opened?
Could there be something inside?
The flowers from the wreath you made.
Red flowers.
Let me tell you,
I think the key clue is here.
I want to see if there's a complete sword inside.
I feel we're very, very close to the key evidence today.
You need to take the first spot before he does.
Whether we vote correctly or not, we can still win.
Then if I were the killer,
wouldn't I actively look for my alibi?
Right? Right, right.
But actually, I was just there.
This is actually enough to make him less of a suspect.
We open this door,
lure them over like this,
then just block and lock this door, right?
Is this that dead body?
Because this head looks electrocuted, like a charred, black beluga.
It's a very smart...
creature.
Creature, yes.
I think it could figure out a lot of things.
A room just has anti-collision strips,
right?
That doesn't prove anything.
Actually,
As long as I'm out in the open,
I'll mess up all the games.
You won't have a single chance.
Just this... this one.